Episode 1 How could this have happened?
I can't believe.
We totally fell for it.
Let's go.
Having managed to halt the
lover's invasive attack,
Jotaro and company choose to avoid
the political unrest in Iran and Iraq,
and instead cross the Arabian Sea at Karachi
to arrive at the United Arab Emirates.
Now then, if you'd be so kind
as to sign this document,
everything will be squared away, sir.
Hmm.
Right here, yes?
Man, oh man.
You know, I'm the kind of guy who'd
do almost anything for a pretty girl,
even by a car.
My, aren't you sweet.
How would you feel about the two
of us having dinner sometime?
Sorry, Polnareff.
I hate to interrupt when you're
obviously so busy, but... Mr. Joestar!
Come on, it's time to leave.
Seriously.
Try not to mess with the hair.
Do you know how hard it is
to make it look this good?
as if anybody cares about your hairdo.
You're driving.
Radio.
Au River, mademoiselle.
Hey, Mr. Joestar,
I don't get why we're
riding in such a fancy,
expensive car in this sandy death trap.
Wouldn't it be better for us to
get an off-road vehicle instead?
Oh, there's a method to my madness.
C 'est magnifique!
This country's amazing!
Are you guys seeing what I am here?
It's like every house is a
crazy mansion or something.
Yeah.
In Tokyo, a house like one of these
would cost 3 or 4 billion yen.
However, for most people in this
country, it's standard living.
It wasn't but 20 years ago that
this place was a barren desert,
Though thanks to a thriving oil industry,
it's grown into a playground for the rich.
The sun is merciless, but at
least with air conditioning,
it's perfectly comfortable inside the car.
So no complaints here.
Huh?
What's wrong, Kakyoin?
It's nothing.
I was just thinking about
how open it is here.
I know we could spot anyone following us,
but I just can't shake the feeling that
there's someone out there watching.
Yeah, can't say that I blame you.
Well, back to business.
I've given a bit of thought
to the route we should take.
About 100 kilometers northwest
is a village called Yarplein.
The desert and mountains make taking
a direct route near impossible.
It normally takes two
days to reach my car.
So to expedite the travel time, the
locals use a Cessna to get there.
If you want my opinion,
we should go to the
village and buy a Cessna
in order to cross the
vast Saudi Arabian desert.
You know, I've been apprehensive
about getting anywhere near a plane.
If a stand user attacked
and the plane went down,
we'd be putting innocent
lives in harm's way.
But if we had a Cessna,
I could be the pilot.
We'd be able to save a
couple of days for sure.
Flying in a Cessna with a man
who's been in three plane crashes.
Yeah, that seems like
a perfect idea to me.
That comment notwithstanding,
our priority should be
crossing the desert.
and hightailing it to
the village of Yarpline.
It'll take us one day on Camelback.
Camelback?
A Cessna is one thing, but on Camelback?
I've never ridden a camel in my life!
Just leave everything to me.
I know these creatures well, and
I'll teach you how to ride them.
You boys sit back and
watch the magic happen.
You want camels, you say?
Sure I have them, but
they're gonna cost you,
my friend, and they need a gentle touch.
We're kind of in a life-or-death situation
here, so we need them, whatever it takes.
As for payment, how about
a trade for that car?
I couldn't possibly accept such a
generous offer! Yeah, Mr. Joestar!
And besides, you literally
just bought that car!
What other reason did you think I had
to buy such a fancy, expensive car?
It's true an off-road vehicle
would perform better here,
but we're not in the big city.
We can't just write a check in this place.
And cash isn't accepted here.
In my experience, trading is far more
effective in places such as these.
If you try to buy safety for
cheap in a time of emergency,
you'll find yourself even
worse off in the end.
Besides, I don't know about you, but
I think we've suffered enough already.
Hey, mister! Huh?
I take it this seals the deal?
Oh, hey, you know what?
To make things a little more even, I'd
like the water in those tanks, too.
It's the most important thing
when you're in the desert.
But the water isn't nearly
as valuable as your car, sir.
You are very strange indeed, sir.
All right, everyone.
Let's get ready, shall we?
Crossing the desert will be no easy task.
Brace yourselves, men.
Man, that stinks!
Hey, Mr.
Joestar, how the heck are we supposed
to get on one of these things?
It's like three meters tall!
Allow me to demonstrate the
proper way to mount a camel.
You have to make them sit
first and then you get on.
Like I said, make them
sit and then get on.
You see, just like this.
You make them sit, and
then you get on them.
Give me a minute.
Any second this beast is gonna
sit, then let me saddle up.
Hey, sit down, would you?
Damn it, you star! Mr.
Joe Star, you have ridden one
of these before, haven't you?
I will have you know that
I've watched Lawrence
of Arabia three times
now from start to finish.
I know all too well how to ride a camel,
although two of those times
I slept through half of it.
You learned to ride from a movie?
So you're saying you've never
actually ridden one before?
The saliva makes great
sunscreen, the more you know.
Listen up.
When you're handling an animal,
it's absolutely imperative to
understand exactly how it feels.
And I mean exactly.
Here, doesn't this yummy apple
look absolutely scrumptious?
It's really good.
Come on.
There's a good boy.
You see?
I made the camel sit down.
If you just take the time to get inside
its head, it'll sit down for you for sure.
Whoa, I did it!
Whoa, it's so high off the ground.
By the way, did you know camels?
Can close their nostrils to keep
the sand out and before I forget,
you're forbidden from
making Stupid camel jokes!
Is that understood?
Your turn now, you greenhorns!
Get to learn the finer
points Of riding a camel!
Listen up!
The first thing you need to know is that
camels don't walk anything Like horses!
The front and back legs on either
side move forward together,
so these things can sway a Lot
but don't let that throw you off!
If you find a way to ride with a camel's
rhythm, I know you'll Be just fine!
For example!
Yeah! Hey! Wait!
You're going too fast!
Slow down!
Listen to me! Damn it! Yeah!
I didn't tell you to go that way!
Okay!
Then now that everyone's gotten the hang
of mounting and riding their camels!
All right!
We have a desert to get through!
The time has arrived! Men!
Onward toward the northwest!
Hey, now, wait just a minute!
Hey!
Something's wrong.
Huh?
I still haven't been able to shake the
feeling that someone out
there is watching us.
Hmm?
Kakyoin, don't you think you
might be worrying a bit too much?
I mean the palm leaves
will erase our tracks.
Plus, we can see for
kilometers in all directions.
If someone were here, we'd know.
Actually, I think he's on to something.
I feel some sort of presence, too.
Hey, Jotaro, why don't you go take a look?
How about it?
Do you see anything suspicious out there?
No, nothing.
Nothing whatsoever.
Even so, something's not right here.
But what is it?
Hey, let's hurry up and go.
Yeah.
Let's get as far away as we can.
We'll keep pressing forward until
the sun goes down this evening,
then stop to pitch our tents.
It's much too dangerous
for us to travel at night.
I only wish we could get
out of this freaking heat.
Just look at this.
It's reading 50 degrees Celsius.
Yeah, it is hot out here.
But then again, the weather is
at its hottest right around now.
Eight o 'clock? What?
Jotaro, check your watch.
What time does it say?
It's ten past eight.
Hey, old man!
My watch is correct.
We lost track of time, but...
What the hell's going on?
According to my watch, it's past 8 p .m.
So why isn't the sun setting?
This is impossible.
The thermometer is jumping
to 60 degrees Celsius.
No, the sun isn't setting at all.
It's actually...
It's actually rising higher in the west!
Wait, could it be that
that sun is really...
A stand?
I don't understand how such
a thing is even possible!
How could this sun actually be a stand?
Quickly, take cover behind those rocks!
How the hell could that sun be a stand?
We're such fools!
How did we miss this?
I knew that we were being watched,
but I never thought this is
why I couldn't see our stalker.
At this rate, that sauna's
gonna burn all day.
No, all night long.
Oh, nom de dieu!
It's going to roast us like a
bunch of rotisserie chickens!
We're totally screwed!
Yeah.
Though I doubt it'll take that long.
The thing is, a sauna can dangerously
raise the body's temperature in minutes.
Okay, then how do we fight it?
C 'est des conneries!
It's 70 degrees Celsius!
And to add insult to injury, we can't
tell if the stand is close or not.
The distance is impossible to judge.
Our only option here is to
quickly take out the stand user.
Indeed, the user.
He has to be nearby.
We have to find him.
He must have a way to conceal himself.
And somehow he's been
following us all this time.
Hang on a minute.
What if it's like the lovers
we encountered in Pakistan?
Maybe this guy has a stand
he can use from far away.
Hey, that's not the case this time.
Sure, a weak STAN can be
controlled from a distance,
but this sun is just too strong.
The energy it's emitting is incredible.
The STAN user has to be nearby.
Hey, check it out.
The camels are starting to
collapse from exposure to the heat,
and this wading isn't getting us anywhere.
I'll use Hierophant to do some
reconnaissance around the area.
Kakyoin, I'm only searching
for the stand's rough location.
Once we know how far away it actually is,
we might just be able to locate the user.
20 meters, 40 meters, 60
meters, 80 meters, 100!
Something's not right.
Kakyoin, have Hierophant come back!
There's something coming right at us!
Before that happens, Emeralds!
No!
Can't go in!
The camel!
You bastards!
I'm gonna bust a hole in the ground!
Everyone get in now! Hurrah!
You okay, Kakyoin?
Yes, I am.
I was in the middle of
initiating my Emerald Splash,
so that protected me
from any major damage.
More concerning is this intense heat.
I feel like it's going to drive me insane.
Did any of you notice that
attack was perfectly aimed at us?
And that could only mean that
the enemy has been watching us.
But from where? Where is he?
Polnareff, keep your voice down.
If you keep shouting,
the enemy will find us.
Just lay low for now.
We'll sit tight for a while
and see what happens next.
Hmm?
Oh, shit!
Things can't go on like this.
Come on, think! Damn it!
It's time for this old timer
to take the bull by the horns!
But this isn't the most ideal spot.
I can't even use my best technique!
It's crucial.
that I get more information.
Jotaro!
Son of a bitch!
Where the hell are you?
How are you watching us?
Are you invisible or something?
Show yourself, you coward! Damn!
Let's go.
already.
Control yourself, man.
Jotaro!
This is happening to you, too?
Polarib! No!
Not you, too!
Oh, my God! No!
They've all lost it!
This damn heat has driven
them all completely insane.
I have my sanity, but what can I do?
Hey, Jotaro, get a hold of yourself, man.
You have to settle down.
You need to listen to me, Jotaro.
Sometimes things get rough, but when
they do, you have to remain in control.
Please, please don't get the
wrong idea about this, Mr.
Joestar.
Have a look at that rock over there.
It's large enough for someone
to hide behind, don't you agree?
What I don't follow you.
Oh you will now take a look at the rock
that's sitting on the opposite side.
Opposite side huh.
Um you still don't see it sir?
Have another look there's
a rock that's exactly
the same way but it's
on the opposite side.
The shadow is also reversed which means?
What a stupid trick!
Move.
Stay here, old man.
Jotaro!
If you go out there now, you're all
but asking for the enemy to attack you!
It's dangerous!
How'd a hole suddenly appear in thin air?
Good grief, old man.
You really are pathetic.
Well,
I'll just assume that the intense
heat was too much for you or
else I'd find it very hard to
believe that you're my grandfather.
Since we defeated the enemy stand,
night's finally fallen or maybe I
should say it's back to being night.
However, you want to slice it.
We're safe at last Just how long
do you plan on hiding in that hole?
Oh, yeah, right?
Good grief.
It's finally gotten dark around here
Well, what do you know?
It's a mirror.
And look at this.
Check out the little car
he's got behind the mirror.
It looks like it's rather comfy.
There's even air conditioning.
Man,
I had no clue he was
reflecting the desert and
tailing us from behind him
this nifty little thing.
He was smarter than I thought.
I see he has a tank of water, too.
How about we take it off his hands?
Oh, and here's a drink.
Huh?
Let me understand all this.
You mean, we've already
defeated the stand user?
There's nothing else to do?
We don't even know this guy's name!
But somehow we've already
made short work of his stand?
Yes, you've hit the nail on the head.
So this was the sun card stand, huh?
At first he was pretty impressive.
But once we figured the guy out, he
actually kind of sucked, didn't he?
So, off to our next destination.
It's pretty chilly in the
desert at night, isn't it?
Hold your horses.
Traveling at night is dangerous.
If we're not careful,
we could lose our way.
Yeah, and with that idiot out of the
way, it'll be sweet dreams tonight.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types of the hookah. Walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses.
Take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian?
Aaaaaah!
Uuuuh. T-t-t! Aaaaaah!
Aaaah!
Aaaaaah!